ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
ShinY
深影
好了 记住
All right, remember,
■
ShinY
深影
放松肩部 用横膈膜发声
loose shoulders, let your diaphragm do the rest,
■
翻译：  黑猫 Miah Elena AlliumFistulosum 鲜虾鱼板面
十七年前
还有 高音时不要紧张
and don't tense up when you hit the high notes.
妈妈我做不到 这样好疼
Mom, I can't. It hurts.
■
校对：  负零     压制： 青鸟
- 肚子疼而已 - 不是我的肚子
- It's just a little tummy ache. - It's not my tummy.
- 是我的肋骨 - 我怎么跟你说
- It's my side. - What am I gonna say to you?
疼痛代表着软弱正在离开身体
Pain is weakness leaving the body.
ShinY
深影
■
这就对了 我们是赢家
That's right. We are winners.
这意味着我们要不惜一切代价获胜
And that means that we do whatever it takes to win.
上台去 保持微笑
So you go out there and just keep smiling.
好吗 宝贝
Okay, baby?
好吧
All right.
ShinY
深影
你看起来真美
You look beautiful.
ShinY
深影
下一位登场的 是来自爱荷华州 得梅因
Next up, from Des Moines, Iowa...
十五号选手
... contestant 15,
星光
Starlight.
我这辈子 各种有权有势的人
My whole life, rich people, powerful people
试图让我闭嘴 让我消失
tried to muzzle me, cancel me,
让我一无是处 让我唯命是从
keep me... me impotent and... and obedient,
好像我就是个傀儡
like I'm a puppet.
- 起作用了 - 艾希莉
- You know what? It worked. - Hey, Ashley,
危机管理部怎么说
what's crisis management saying about this?
不好意思 星光 不是现在
Sorry, Starlight, not now!
猜猜怎么着
And guess what.
如果他们能够控制我 就一定能够
If they can control me, then you can
控制你们
bet your ass they can control you.
他们已经这么做了 只是你们还不知道
They're already doing it. You just don't realize it.
我受够了
I'm done.
我受够了道歉
I am done apologizing.
我受够了因为我的能力而被压迫
I am done being persecuted for my strength.
受够了因为我的能力而被压迫
...done being persecuted for my strength.
因为我的能力而被压迫
...persecuted for my strength.
被压迫 被压迫 被压迫
...persecuted... persecuted... persecuted...
你升高了
You're up!
升高了
- 不敲门的吗 - 该死 对不起
- No knock? - Oh, fuck, I'm sorry.
我等会再来
Um, I'm... Yeah, I'm gonna come back later.
等等
Wait.
你说我升高了是什么意思
What do you mean, I'm up?
升高了二十一点
21 points with your base.
你说什么
What did you just say to me?
二十一点 他们爱死你的演讲了
21 points. They loved your speech.
男屌丝支持率大幅度增长了四十四点
A massive 44% uptick with white males in the Rust Belt.
- 太好了 - 我知道
- Yes. - I know.
牛X 简直了
Fuck yes. Yes!
他们说你自信且毫无歉意
They're saying you're confident and unapologetic
你不畏惧
and that you're not afraid to...
继续说 艾希莉 别停
Keep fucking going, Ashley. Don't stop.
- 不好意思 先生 - 什么
- Um, I'm sorry, sir. - What?
跟你无关
Uh... That's got nothing to do with you.
继续说 不畏惧什么
Just keep going. Not afraid to what?
不畏惧做你自己
Not afraid to be yourself.
他们想让我做我自己
They want me to be myself?
现在
Now, um...
城区十八到三十四岁成年组支持率下滑了七点
...you did slip seven points with urban-area adults 18 to 34.
但不算糟 很好
But it's not bad. It's good.
因为 从根本上说
Because ultimately, everybody
所有人都喜欢你和星光的组合
loves you and Starlight as a team.
你们在一起时的受欢迎程度达到百分之九十八
Together, you have a Q Rating of 98%.
史无前例
No one's ever been that high.
士兵男孩也没有 前无古人
Not Soldier Boy, not anyone.
九十八
Ninety-eight.
如果我回来 你就得管好你自己
I'm-a be back, you got to police your shit.
这是熨斗大厦
This is the Flatiron Building.
这可是座历史悠久的建筑
It's a historic motherfucking building.
我们得尊重它的名声
We got to put some respect on the building's name.
瞧瞧
Look at this.
拿个盘子
Use a plate.
我舔你妈那美味的阴道时
But I don't use a plate when I eat
可没有用盘子
your mother's sweet and savory vagin.
山崎纪在干嘛
What is Kimiko doing?
- 你在逗我吗 拜托 - 嘿 嘿 拜托
- Are you kidding me? Come on. - Oh, hey, hey. Come on.
拜托 她一直都忍受着
Come on. She's been suffering
无所事事的折磨 好吗
the dreary sting of ennui, okay?
给她些空间
You give her some space.
- 浪子归来了 - 什么鬼
- The prodigal son returns. - What the fuck?
嘿 兄弟
Hey, man.
等等 等等 你 你回来了
Yeah, wait, wait, wait, wait. Are you t... Are you back?
走着瞧
We'll see.
别理解错了 我很高兴 但你确定吗
Don't get me wrong, I'm happy, but are... are you sure?
这是怎么了 孩子
What the fuck happened here, kid?
你又用剃须刀自慰了
You jacking off with razors again?
你应该看看另一个
You know, you should see the other guy.
也就是我的屌
Other guy's my penis.
- 我很想你 孩子 - 我也很想你 兄弟
- I missed you, kid. - I missed you, too, man.
来吧 兄弟
Come on, man.
听着 我知道你要说什么 我只是
Look, I know what you're gonna say, and I just...
不 不 伙计 我只是很高兴
No, no, mate. I'm just chuffed
黑袍纠察队的人重聚一堂 好吗
to have all the Boys back under the same roof, all right?
- 真的吗 - 没错
- Really? - Yeah.
他在那里 对吗
I mean, there he was, right?
穿着他昂贵的裤子
In his fancy pants,
就像沃特广场的总督一样管着我们
lording it over us like the viceroy of Vought Square, eh?
那段时间里 他什么都是不
And that whole time, he weren't nothing
- 除了超人类的马屁精 - 是啊
- but a Supe's bootlick, eh? - Yeah.
为此 孩子 你都可以拿到
That, my son, is a Lifetime Achievement
- 年度傻X奖之终生成就奖了 - 是啊
- at the Cunt of the Year Awards, isn't it? - Yeah, it is.
确实是终生成就
It is a Lifetime Achievement.
- 你说完了吗 - 还没有呢 伙计
- Are you done? - No, mate,
相信我 我才刚刚起了个头
I am just getting started, believe you me.
好极了 听着 我们要把瑞恩带去安全的地方
Great, listen, we need to get Ryan somewhere safe.
维琪知道他在哪因为我们告诉了她
Vicky knows where he is, because we fucking told her,
这意味着斯坦·埃德加也知道
which means Stan Edgar knows, too.
我们领先一步
Yeah, one step ahead.
上校已经带着那个孩子转移了
Colonel's already done a runner with the boy.
他们已经藏起来了
They're well out of sight.
事实上 我们要去拜访他们
In fact, we were gonna pay them a little visit.
是吗
We are?
布彻先生 我去不了
Uh, Monsieur Charcutier, uh, I cannot go.
- 我有很重要的事 - 不好意思
- I have a matter of great importance. - Oh, I'm sorry.
我想必是忘记告知你那该死的秘书了
I must've forgot to run it by your bleeding secretary.
- 紧急情况 - 我可以替他
- It's an emergency. - I... I'll go instead.
你要是今天不去上班
Nah, you skive off today,
那个国会女议员可能会把你爆菊
and that congresswoman might split your pretty little buns.
我也想到了
Yeah, thought of that.
山崎纪
Uh, Kimiko.
山崎纪 嘿
Kimiko? Hi.
你能帮我 把胳膊弄折吗
Uh, can you please... uh, break my arm?
我要是装病 会被维琪发现的
Vicky will smell it if I fake being sick,
所以得真实点 还得能持续几天
so it's got to be real, and it's got to last for days.
我日 休伊
Fucking hell, Hughie.
至少吃点止痛药吧
At least take something for the pain.
我有鸦片
I got opium.
公务员尿检不能呈阳性
Government employees can't fail a piss test.
让我们速战速决 好吧
Let's just get this over with, okay?
下手利索点
Just do it pretty fast.
等等 等等
H... Hold, hold, hold up.
请坐
Have a seat, please.
才来三分钟
Only been here three minutes,
就他妈要见血了
and it's already The Bold and the Batshit.
好吧 来吧
All right. Go ahead.
好了
Okay.
就这儿
Right here.
动作要快 不要有永久性损伤
Clean break. No permanent damage.
一 二
One, two...
什么鬼
What the shit?
我是第一位穆斯林超人类女性
I'm the first Super in a hijab, aren't I?
所以如果我能进入七人队的话就太棒了
So if I can get myself into The Seven, lit, man.
我们在考虑让超音速第一个上
So, we're thinking slot one goes to Supersonic.
对十一到十四岁的女孩来说
For girls 11 to 14,
他是个不折不扣的高富帅
he's a real panty-dropper.
这太可怕了 拜托以后别再说这种话了
That's horrifying. Please never say that again.
他在拉丁市场上也会大放异彩
He's also a slam dunk for the Latinx market.
我们非常渴望能进军中美和南美市场
We are desperate to get into Central and South America.
你知道莎莎酱比番茄酱更受欢迎吗
Did you know that salsa is more popular than ketchup?
超音速是一位雄心勃勃的
Is Supersonic an ambitious second-generation
第二代墨西哥裔美国人 加入七人队
Mexican American chasing his lifelong sue?
- 是他毕生追逐的梦想吗 - 亦或
- of joining The Seven? - Or is he chasing
他是想和星光旧情复燃呢
a rekindled passion with Starlight?
行了 你们知道我有男朋友 对吧
Okay, you do know that I have a boyfriend, right?
你们的三角恋上了热搜
Love triangles, they generate a 47% surge
关注度激增四十七点
in trending topics on social platforms.
粉丝们磕CP磕得飞起
Fans will ship the fuck out of you.
让我先跟他谈谈
Let me talk to him first.
好极了 你对我们的第二选择有什么想法
Amazing. Uh, what do you think of our second choice?
- 月影 - 她身材很好
- Moonshadow. - She's body positive
- 又不至于太过火 - 很撩人
- but not too body positive. - Still fuckable.
非常撩人
So fuckable.
没人问你 艾希莉
No one asked you, Ashley.
对不起 艾希莉
Sorry, Ashley.
好吧 这也很可怕
Okay, that's also horrifying,
但我考虑的是希尔芙·金坎德
but I'm thinking Silver Kincaid.
但是她
But she's, uh...
她来自阿富
She's from Afghan...
- 她来自英格兰 - 汗
- She's from England. - ...istan?
所有决赛选手中
And she has the highest rescue stats
她的复活支持率最高
of any of the finalists, and she's
她还是联合国儿童基金会的大使
a UNICEF ambassador.
她是最有资格的
She's the most qualified.
当然了 这些都得跟祖国人
Well, we're gonna have to run all of this past Homelander,
- 说一下 - 当然了
- of course. - Of course.
事实上 就我和埃德加先生达成的协议来看
Actually, according to my contract with Mr. Edgar,
我对这两个位置有最终决定权
I get final say over the two slots.
所以 你不如把这话告诉祖国人
So, why don't you run that past Homelander,
你好 雪莉
Bonjour, Cherie.
你把护照带来了吗
Did you bring the passports?
嘿
Hey.
怎么了
What is wrong?
塞尔奇 我搞杂了
Serge, I fucked up.
我转头回去为小妮娜工作
I went back to work for Little Nina.
天呐 雪莉
Merde, Cherie.
不是每个人都能在中情局找到一份轻松的工作
Some of us can't get cushy jobs at the CIA.
我为她运货
I was moving weight for her,
但那些该死的混蛋把货给偷了
and these fucking assholes boosted it.
你能找到他们吗
Can you find them?
他们带着面具 我不知道他们是谁
They wore masks. I don't know who they were.
况且我当时也嗨了
And I was high.
好吧
Okay.
有多少
How much?
11公斤
Eleven kilos.
我们给她钱
We pay her back.
我们把钱还给她 祈求她...
We pay her back. We beg...
没用的 你知道妮娜的原则是
No, you know it's the principle of the thing with Nina.
你记得奥利弗吗
You remember Olivier?
她把他活剐了
How many pieces did she cut off him while he was still alive?
跟我走
Come with me.
去温暖的地方
We can go someplace warm.
就咱俩
Just you and me.
对不起
Sorry.
马文 你在这儿干吗呢
Oh, Marvin. What are you doing here?
判断失误 女士
Poor judgment, ma'am.
布彻
Butcher!
嗨
Hi.
轻点小伙子
Oh, easy does it, lad.
真够有劲儿的啊
Bloody death grip you got there.
- 你还好吗 - 是的
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
一点事儿都没有
Right as rain.
进来吧
Come on in.
这他妈发生了啥
The fuck was that?
心有猛虎细嗅蔷薇吗
Didn't know he had it in him.
你到底为啥回来
So, why did you come back?
士兵男孩杀了我全家
Soldier Boy killed my family.
你确定这地方安全吗
Are you sure this place is secure?
我们得不停换地方 但这里暂时安全
We'll have to keep moving, but for now, yes.
唯一能让我们暴露的事情
The only thing that might give us away
就是你旁若无人的出现在我家门口
is this clown show of yours shambling onto my driveway.
好吧...
Well...
如果一通电话就能解决 我肯定不会过来
I wouldn't be here if this was just a phone call.
阿莱克斯来一下
Hey, Alex, just, um, come here for a second.
你干嘛放我的烂歌
Um, why are you playing my shitty song?
这样他就听不见了
So he can't hear us.
他们想把你选为今晚的获胜者
They want to pick you as one of the winners tonight.
认真的吗
- Are you serious? - Mm-hmm.
你要拒绝提名
And you need to say no.
- 什么 为什么 - 听好了
- What? Why? - Okay, listen.
我真希望当初有人
I really wish someone told me
告诉我这些
what I'm about to tell you.
祖国人有问题
There's something wrong with Homelander.
心理问题
Something broken.
他不止一次威胁说要杀了我
He's threatened to murder me more than once.
他还杀过其他人 一切只会变得更糟
He's murdered other people, and it's only getting worse.
你若获胜 只会让你自己
And you're just gonna be putting yourself
和家人受到牵连
and your family in danger.
其他人也难逃一死
And pretty much the rest of them, too.
他们残忍极了 相信我
They're so fucking cruel. Trust me,
超乎你的想象 就说你做不到
you don't want this. Just say that you can't do it.
说家里突然有急事找你
Say that your family is having an emergency.
- 别去领奖 - 安妮 安妮 等一下
- Don't do it. - Annie, Annie, Annie, stop... Annie, Annie, stop.
你刚刚告诉我
You just told me that...
这些年我忍受的恶心事儿 还有乐队
all the shit I swallowed for years... I mean, the band,
沃特的种族歧视 都白费了 对吧
Vought's racism, it's all for, it's all for nothing, right?
- 听着 我... - 听着 我得缓缓
- Look, I'm so... - Look, I need a second.
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry, but, please,
但是拜托了 向我保证你会离开
you need to promise me that you will leave
而且再也不回来 求你了
and you'll never look back. Please.
他们给你配了专车吗
So they chauffeuring you around now, huh?
和蕾哈娜一个待遇
Like you Rihanna.
从不需要驾照 我直接跑就行
Never needed a license, always just ran.
- 你怎么知道我在这 - 我是你兄弟
- How'd you know I'd be here? - I'm your brother.
我还有点儿路子
And I still know a few people.
所以
So...
情况有多糟糕
how bad is it?
医生说和俄罗斯轮盘一样
Doctors say it's like playing Russian roulette.
如果我再跑 可能啥事都没有
If I ever run again, maybe nothing,
也可能我的心脏...
but maybe my heart...
你还在吃那药呢
You still on that blue shit?
吃那个药我估计死得更快
That shit'll probably kill me even faster.
好极了 那我们可以快进到我接受你的道歉
Good. Then we can skip to the part where I accept your apology
然后你和我一起回家的部分了
and you can come back to the crib with me.
孩子们都很想见到你
Sure the boys would love to see you, man.
布彻说你有超能力
Butcher said you have powers.
我也有
Me, too.
你喜欢自己的能力吗
Do you like yours?
你会因此感到害怕吗
Do you ever get scared of them?
我也是
Me, too.
格蕾丝阿姨希望给我买条狗
Aunt Grace wanted to get me a dog, but...
但我拒绝了
I told her no.
我害怕会伤到它
I was afraid I'd hurt it.
我明白 我伤害过别人
我相信你不是故意的
I'm sure you didn't mean it.
我讨厌我的超能力 要是没有就好了
是的
Yeah.
我也是
Me, too.
纽曼成为局长是因为我的决定
Neuman's head of the bureau because I said so.
她就是袭击国会的凶手
I tried to save her from
我却还想着救她
the attack on Congress that she fucking caused.
至少你没有过去一整年
Well, at least you didn't spend the last year
都给她准备燕麦拿铁
getting her oat milk lattes
和她要求的每一份情报
and every piece of intel she asked for.
我对干掉她的计划十分感兴趣
I would very much like to know the plan to eliminate her.
这取决于
Well, that depends
你在多大程度上告诉我们
on what you can tell us
你在尼加拉瓜度假时发生了什么
about your little holiday down in Nicaragua.
- 我从没去过尼加拉瓜 - 真的吗
- I've never been to Nicaragua. - Really?
但有只小鸟告诉我
'Cause a little birdie told me
你是当时复仇小队的负责人
you were Payback's case officer down there,
士兵男孩因为
on a classified job
某次秘密行动再也没回来
that Soldier Boy never come back from.
上校
Colonel?
不论威廉认为他听到了什么消息
Whatever it is William thinks he may have heard,
他都听错了
he's mistaken.
是吗
Is he?
你家的办公室里
You know that safe
有个保险箱对吧
you got in your home office?
在老布什照片后面的那个
The one behind the picture of Bush number one?
我从里面借了一个账簿
Well, I borrowed a ledger from it,
里面记录了你在世界各地的特工
the one with all your assets around the world.
你觉得我把他们的名字曝光到脸书上之后
How long do you think them and their families will last
他们和他们的家人能活多久
when I put every one of their fucking names on Facebook?
你会让几十位无辜的普通人
You'd sign the death warrants of dozens of innocent people
因为这件事命丧黄泉吗
who had nothing to do with this?
你问得这个问题让咱们都很难堪
I'm embarrassed for the both of us that you're asking.
尼加拉瓜是陈年往事了
Nicaragua's ancient history.
更不要说告诉你 我就有可能被杀
Not to mention I could be killed just for telling you.
你不说的话 你所有的特工都会死
And all your agents will get killed if you don't.
天啊
Blimey.
真是难题
What a pickle.
那是查理行动的一部分
It was part of Operation Charly.
查理...
Operation...
行动...
Charly?
里根的小项目 非官方的
Reagan's pet project, off the books.
为了帮助反叛军去打受俄罗斯支援的桑迪诺
Help the Contra rebels fight the Russian-backed Sandinistas,
但是我们得想个法子付钱
but we needed a way to pay for it.
一些现金来自向伊朗倒卖武器
Some of the cash came from selling arms to Iran,
奥利弗·诺斯做的史诗级蠢事
Oliver North's epic fuckup.
剩下的呢
But the rest?
如果说反对派有什么资源是充足的
If there's one thing that the Contras had plenty of,
那就是可卡因
it was cocaine.
我负责把可卡因运进美国境内
I was in charge of trafficking the coke into the U.S.
用贩毒的利润去买更多的武器
and then using the profits to buy more weapons.
对抗共产主义时
In the fight against the Reds,
我们不惜一切代价
whatever it took.
净说些自我狡辩的屁话
That's some self-justifying bullshit.
另外的事情你也参与了是吗
Were you part of that other thing, too?
什么另外的事儿
What other thing?
她知道
She knows.
告诉他
Tell him.
有一个不成文的规定
The unwritten policy
可卡因只能在特定的少数族裔社群进行贩卖
was to sell the cocaine strictly to minority neighborhoods.
让少数族裔变得不稳定 堕落  不影响白人
Destabilize, demoralize, while staying out of white ones.
八四年年底 我们正为一次大规模进攻做准备
Late in '84, we were gearing up for a major offensive,
所以高层运用了他们智慧的脑壳
so the higher-ups, in their infinite wisdom,
认为这是一个搞破坏的绝佳时期
decided it was the perfect time to throw a wrench in the works.
天杀的复仇小队
Fucking Payback.
每一个人都可笑之极
Each more ridiculous than the next.
绯红伯爵夫人 头脑风暴
Crimson Countess, Mindstorm,
虫人 炸药双包胎
Swatto, the TNT Twins,
玄色 火药
Noir, Gunpowder,
和其中最傻X的一个...
and the most idiotic of them all...
火药 你意下如何
What do you say, Gunpowder?
让他们感受下国庆氛围吧
Give them the Fourth of July?
士兵男孩 让它们燃起来
Let's light them up, Soldier Boy.
请放下武器
Please put that down.
好吧
Ah, well,
我没意识到负责人能长得像这么好看
didn't realize they made case officers as pretty as you.
我们就是找找乐子
We're just having some fun.
我们的军火库就是那个方向
Our munitions dump is in that direction.
你这样会炸毁一半的营地
You're about to blow up half the camp.
放下
Put it down.
立刻
Now.
我喜欢强势的女人
I do like the assertive type.
你身材这么好
You know, with a figure like yours,
在这儿呆着浪费了
you are wasted down here.
请接受我的道歉
My humblest apologies.
肯定是有什么误解
I'm sure this is... disorienting.
我们重新来过 指挥官格蕾丝·马洛里 是吗
Let's start over. Officer Grace Mallory, isn't it?
- 是的 - 斯坦福·埃德加
- Mm. - Stanford Edgar.
我是沃特美国的合伙人
I'm an associate with Vought American.
你愿意解释一下这些怪胎
Do you want to explain what the fuck
想干什么吗
this freak show's all about?
沃特美国已经和美国政府开始合作
Vought American has entered into a partnership
旨在全球范围内打击共产主义
with the U.S. Government in the global war against communism.
- 这样啊 - 复仇小队也会加入其中
- Oh. - Payback will embed themselves
和反叛军并肩作战
and fight alongside the Contra rebels.
把这个看成试运行吧
Think of it as a trial run.
什么试运行
A trial run for what?
当然是超级英雄加入军队
Superheroes in the military, of course.
这是三十多年来的首次尝试
For the first time in over 30 years.
想象一下我们会多战无不胜
Just imagine how dominant we'd be.
天啊 给我下来
Jesus Christ. Get down!
有问题吗
What's the problem?
问题就是
The... problem
敌军可能看到一个傻X人类在丛林上空飞
is that the enemy might spot a fucking flying man
然后找到我们的位置
above the tree line and find our position.
她是对的 虫人
She's right, Swatto.
没有马洛里长官的批准不可以飞行
No flights without Officer Mallory's clearance.
开玩笑吧
Is this a joke?
超级英雄不是士兵
Supes aren't soldiers.
他们是毫无纪律的傻瓜 未经训练 未经测试
They're undisciplined dipshits. Untrained and untested.
他们不属于战区
They do not belong in a war zone.
只属于"不可思议"节目
They belong on That's Incredible!
士兵男孩可不会买账
Tell that to Soldier Boy.
他是一个活生生的美国英雄
He's a living, breathing American hero.
我不允许
I'm not allowing this.
我相信凯希局长会解决
I'm sure Director Casey will address
任何你可能有的担忧
any concerns you may have.
还有 我们需要你派几个人
Oh, and, uh, we need a couple of your men
为我们的帐篷打水
to fetch water for our tents.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
克劳迪奥
Claudio.
今年大都会队没有胜算
Mets don't stand a chance in hell this year.
让洋基队去死吧
fuck the Yankees.
其他人会跟着去吗
Will the others go along?
除了火药 其他人都去
Everyone but Gunpowder.
祝你好运 欧文
Good luck, Earving.
你能别在我面前
Can you please stop eating those
吃那些吗 我过敏
in front of me. I'm allergic.
听着
So, listen,
如果我要在团队中扮演更核心的角色
if I'm gonna take a more central role on the team,
我想摘掉面具
then I want to lose the mask.
不说话的忍者
Silent ninjas score extremely high
极受七至十岁的男孩喜爱
with boys seven to ten years old.
面具赋予了某种神秘感
The mask lends a certain mystique.
去他妈的神秘感
Well, fuck mystique.
人们甚至不知道面具下是我
People don't even know it's me under this thing.
我连打车都得戴着它
I got to wear it just to get a cab.
复仇小队是本国首屈一指的超级英雄团队
Payback is the country's premier superhero team.
可悲的是 在南部
The whole country. Sadly, a Black member's
黑人成员毫无希望成功
still a nonstarter below the Mason-Dixon.
好吧 我可以更出名
Well, I could be bigger than that.
我可以成为艾迪·墨菲
I could be Eddie Murphy.
我不要戴面具
I'm not wearing the mask.
你随便
Your choice.
一旦你被派去明尼阿波利斯圣保罗都会区
Though, once you're farmed out to Minneapolis-St. Paul,
你会想要这个面具的
you'll want the mask
只是为了保暖
simply for warmth.
你应该多笑笑
You should smile more.
- 我敢打赌 你笑起来很美 - 好吧
- I bet it's a beautiful smile. - Okay, look,
身为货真价实的女性
as an ambassador from Planet Actual Woman,
我要告诉你
I just... I got to tell you,
我知道你认为这些话很有效 但是
I know that you think these lines work, but...
它们确实很有效
Oh, they do.
- 问问洛尼·安德森就知道了 - 没效果
- Just ask Loni Anderson. - They don't,
从来都没有效果
and they never have.
女人们要么是在取悦你 要么是怕你
The women are either humoring you, or they're scared of you,
肯定不喜欢你
but none of them like you.
你知道 如果你再和善一点
You know, if you were a little nicer,
也许你会找到一个男人
maybe you'd find a man,
而不是在这里扮演女同队长
instead of out here playing Captain Lesbo.
嘿 马洛里
Hey, Mallory...
等会再说
Hold that thought.
他到底是怎么了
What the hell is going on with him?
- 她在这里 - 你介意吗
- There she is. - You mind?
- 我只是随便吃一点 - 不
- I'm just grabbing a bite to eat - Nope.
我一点也不介意 所以
I do not mind at all. So...
艾希莉告诉我你选择了
Ashley tells me that you chose
希尔芙·金凯
Silver Kinca...
金凯德
Kincaid.
我都记下了
I have notes.
我是说 我是联合队长
I mean, I'm a cocaptain.
决定新成员人选时 我有发言权才公平 对吧
It's only fair I have a say in the new recruits, right?
不 实际上 选择新成员 我说了算
No, actually, I choose the new members.
但我会展现最出人意料的反转
But I am pitching the craziest twist.
观众永远都猜不到 对吧
The audience will never see it coming, right?
我已经做出了决定
Well, I've made my decision.
拜托 你还没听我说是谁呢
Oh, come on. You haven't even heard it yet.
说真的 你会喜欢的 准备好了吗
Seriously, you're-you're gonna love it. Ready?
深海回归了
Return of the Deep.
嘿
Hey.
大家好吗 你好吗
What's up, guys? How are you?
不不不 星光
No, no, no, no, no, Starlight,
先听我说
before you say anything,
基督不是告诉我们要转过脸去吗
doesn't Christ tell us to turn the other cheek?
我真希望我们能成为姐妹
I really want us to be sisters.
我为你准备了一些东西 星光
I had something made for you, Starlight.
请求跟你和解
It's a peace offering.
二十四K纯金
It's 24-karat gold
有鉴定证书 合法开采的钻石
with certified conflict-free diamonds.
我表达了自己的心意
I've put in the work,
我意识到 犯了不可原谅的错误时
and I realize that when you've made an unforgivable mistake,
你必须先原谅
the first person you have to forgive
你自己
is yourself.
你凭什么认为 我想要跟一个逼我给他口的人
What makes you think that I want a daily reminder
共处一室
of the guy who fucking mouth-raped me?
我得跟你谈谈
I need a word.
让他俩单独聊聊 好吗
Let's let these two chat, shall we?
好的
Okay. I'll just...
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
你真的认为
Do you really think I'm gonna let
我会让一个穆斯林进入七人队吗
a fucking Muslim in The Seven?
基地组织队长 我们可是美国人
Captain Al-Qaeda? We're Americans.
我要跟埃德加先生说说这件事
I'm taking this to Mr. Edgar.
我昨晚的演讲
My speech last night?
好评率38.6% 转发率59%
Thirty-eight-point-six rating and a 59 share.
他们说三天后
Oh, and they're saying that the live-plus-threes
影响力会更大
are gonna be even bigger.
埃德加自己说的
Edgar said it himself,
人气就是力量
popularity is power.
他不会在这个问题上出尔反尔
He won't die on this hill.
需要我提醒你关于三十七号航班的视频吗
Do I need to remind you of the Flight 37 video?
随你
Go ahead.
发布吧
Release it.
去做吧
Let's light this candle, huh?
当然 我会失去一切 但在那之后
I mean, sure, I'll lose everything, but then...
我就没什么可失去的了
I'll have nothing to lose.
首先
First,
我将毁掉指挥机关
I'll take out the nerve centers
白宫 五角大楼
White House, Pentagon
然后 摧毁国内防御力量
then any domestic defense capabilities,
接着是关键性基础设施
and then critical infrastructure
比如说蜂窝网络 互联网之类的
like cellular, Internet, that kind of thing
然后
and then,
我想 到了那时
well, I think then
我会把纽约从这该死的地图上抹去
I'll just wipe New York off the fucking map...
找乐子嘛
for fun.
我甚至还会抹掉得梅因
I'll even throw in Des Moines
以及梅芙那个土里土气的故乡小镇
and that little cousin-fucker hick town
为什么不呢
that Maeve's from, 'cause why not?
看 星光
See, Starlight,
我愿意让别人爱我
I'd prefer to be loved.
我愿意 但如果你把它从我这里夺走
I would, but if you take that away from me,
我不介意
well, being feared
让别人怕我
is A-one okey doke by me.
所以
So
请便吧 搭档
Go ahead, partner.
发布吧
Do it.
不
No?
不想吗
You don't want to do it?
那我不得不说
Well, then I would have to say
你他妈的完全没有筹码
that you have absolutely no fucking leverage
因为我是祖国人
because I am the Homelander.
我他妈的可以为所欲为
And I really can do whatever the fuck I want.
所以明天
Okay, so tomorrow
你跟罗丝·麦高恩和艾莉莎·米兰诺
you have the "Re-Contextualizing Feminism"
一起进行"重新理解女权主义"的小组讨论
panel with Rose McGowan and Alyssa Milano.
我爱看圣女魔咒
Ooh, I love Charmed.
宝贝 我是认真的
Hey, babe, I'm serious.
我们需要保护你
We need to cover your ass
以防星光那个贱人又来找你麻烦
in case that bitch Starlight comes after you again.
谢谢 宝贝 没有你我可做不来
Thanks, babe. I couldn't have done this without you.
可不是嘛
You're telling me.
- 喜欢吗 - 真他妈喜欢
- Yeah, you like that? - Oh, fuck yeah.
老天
Oh, God.
你好湿啊
You're so fucking wet.
都是因为你嘛 宝贝
Oh, it's all you, baby.
都是因为你
It's all you.
你要怎样
What are you gonna do?
用你所有的胳膊给我打飞机吗
Gonna jerk me off with all your arms?
所有的胳膊
All my arms?
布彻 你还好吗
Butcher, are you okay?
好着呢 伙计
Yeah, mate.
一切都好 给我点时间 好吗
It's all good. Just give us a minute, yeah?
需要帮忙吗
Do you need any help?
别进来
Don't come in.
- 嘿 安妮 - 祖国人刚刚崩溃了
- Hey, Annie. - Homelander's had a breakdown.
他完全疯了
He's lost his fucking mind.
嘿 慢点说 怎么了
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Slow down, slow down. What?
他要让深海重新回到七人队
He's bringing the Deep back into The Seven,
所以我提了那段视频的事
so I brought up the video, and he said to go ahead
他叫我随便发布 你之前说的对
and release it. You were right.
做联合队长是个坏主意
Cocaptain was a bad idea.
我得离开
I have to leave.
听着 我知道我应该告诉你赶快逃跑
Look, I know I should tell you to run out of there
我本想这样
like a house on fire, and I want to...
但你必须坚持下去
...but you got to stick it out.
- 什么 - 听着
- I'm sorry? - Listen,
我回去跟布彻干了
I'm-I'm-I'm back with Butcher.
为什么
Why?
我们正在调查某种可以杀死祖国人的武器
We're onto something that could kill Homelander.
什么 是什么
What? What is it?
某种武器
Some kind of weapon. Uh...
我不确定 但你得帮我们争取一些时间
I'm not sure, but you got to buy us some time.
盯着他
Keep your eyes on him.
多长时间
How much time?
你不知道
You don't know.
谁知道要多久呢
So, for God knows how long,
我要强装笑脸
I have to paste on a smile,
而祖国人变得越来越喜怒无常
with Homelander growing more unstable
时时刻刻
by the hour,
希望他不会杀了我 或发生更糟的事
hoping that he doesn't kill me or worse.
如果需要付出那种代价 那就只好如此了
If that's what it takes, then yeah.
抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Just...
我们总是被祖国人和维琪
Homelander and Vicky, they're running laps
牵着鼻子走
around us because...
因为我们太伟光正了
because we keep trying to do it the right way.
事实证明行不通
The high road just doesn't work.
我们必须跟他们一样心狠手辣
W-We have to be as mean and fucked-up as they are.
- 你听起来就像... - 布彻 我知道
- Now you sound like... - Like Butcher, I know,
但 安妮 他... 他是对的
but, Annie, he's... he's right.
他一直都是 我只是...
He's been right all along. I'm just so...
不想再输了
tired of losing.
行吧
Okay.
你最好能搞定 休伊 不过...
You better pull this off, Hughie, but...
行吧
okay.
以前玩打手背 都是我赢的你
I used to destroy you in slapsies.
你有超能力
You had super speed.
卡马里
Khamari.
你有种试试
Put another hand on your brother,
- 再打你弟弟 - 嗨 雷奇叔叔
- you see what happens. - Hey, Uncle Reg,
- 你那衣服是怎么回事 - 你喜欢吗
- what's up with that suit? - Oh, you like it, huh?
- 太老土了 - 卡马里 不许跟你叔叔
- That shit's corny. - Hey, Khamari, that's not
- 那么说话 - 没事
- how you talk to your uncle. - Nah, it's-it's all right.
年轻人不懂历史
Young men just don't understand the history.
并不是 你这身是真的搞笑
Oh, no, the suit's ridiculous.
但他不应该那么说话
But he shouldn't be using that kind of language.
行了 进屋去 你们俩
All right, inside. Both y'all.
好吧 去洗手
All right? And wash your hands.
好好洗
For real this time.
我不想说什么 但...
I didn't want to say nothing, but...
我想告诉这个社区
Just trying to show the community
我为正义而战
I'm down for the cause.
你什么时候变得这么伟大了
Since when you been down with any cause?
别这样 老兄
Come on, man.
我不能跑了 啥都做不了
I mean, I can't run, I can't do shit.
我只能重塑形象
So I got to rebrand.
- 努力不被遗忘 - 也不必如此吧
- Stay in the game somehow. - Or you don't.
你可以继续
You could just be
当我那烦人的小弟弟雷奇
my pain-in-the-ass little brother Reg.
- 嗯 - 这么跟你说吧
- Yeah. - Let me tell you, man,
我训练这些小孩
I'm happier coaching these kids
比在沃特时开心多了
than I ever was working at Vought.
你应该回到跑道上
You should come down to the track.
他们喜欢见到你
They'd love to see you.
是么
Yeah.
行
Okay.
既然你这么想要为正义而战
Since you want to be down with the cause so much...
- 嗯 - 我当时走在回家路上
- Hmm? - I was walking home,
一个抢劫犯来到身后
and this mugger came up behind me.
我吓坏了
I was terrified.
达娜·惠特迈尔说蓝鹰
And that's when Dana Whitmyre says Blue Hawk
就是这个时候救了她
came to her rescue.
大约是傍晚七点十五分
At approximately 7:15 p.M.,
我注意到一名黑人男性尾随被害人
I spotted a Black male following the victim
在马林大道往南方向
southbound on Marin Boulevard.
我截住了他
I intercepted him, at which point
然后该疑犯变得狂暴
the suspect became aggressive.
这兄弟就住在前面几个房子那
Brother lived a few houses up the street.
有三个孩子
Three kids.
他只是走在回家路上
He was just walking home from work.
蓝鹰把他狠狠地踩在路边
Blue Hawk curb-stomped him so hard,
人行道都裂开了
it cracked the pavement.
- 这太可怕了 - 嗯
- That's fucked-up. - Yeah.
或许我可以给他家里人点钱什么的
Maybe I can throw his family some cash or something.
他们需要的不是嗟来之食
They don't need a handout.
他们需要你为他们发声
They need you to speak up.
你是七人队的一员
You're in The motherfucking Seven.
是 但...
Yeah, but, I mean...
听着 我是迈克尔·乔丹
I... Listen, I'm Michael Jordan.
不是马尔科姆·X
I'm not Malcolm X.
人人都爱火车头 对吧
Everybody loves the A-Train, right?
塞尔奇
Sergei.
- 妮娜想要见你 - 叶甫根尼
- Nina wants to see you. - Yevgenny.
你老婆怎么样了
How's your wife?
她还是喜欢和法国人翻江倒海
She still enjoy getting her salad tossed by a Frenchman
对她老公不理不睬吗
while her husband tosses nothing?
下次吧
Another time.
上车
Get in.
拜托 没完没了了
Come on. Fucking knock it off.
你还好吗
All right, mate?
你生病了
Are you sick?
没有 没有
No, no.
吃了点有问题烤肉
I had a dodgy kebab, didn't I?
穿肠而过了
Went straight through me.
尝尝这个
Try these.
好的
Well, I'll be.
你妈妈以前喜欢在我不舒服的时候给我这个
Your mum used to give me these when I was under the weather.
一样
Same.
- 我不喜欢吃 - 我会捣碎
- I hated them. - I used to crush them up
然后趁她不注意 都倒进喂鸟器里
and put them in the bird feeder when she wasn't looking.
的确不怪你
Well, I don't blame you.
这饼干让你嘴巴比修女的... 还干
They done off leave your mouth drier than a nun's...
你是要说阴道吗
You were gonna say "Vagina."
是 差不多吧
Yeah. Something like that.
不过 不单单是你的胃
It's not just your stomach, though.
你心跳很快 我能听到
Your heart's racing. I can hear it.
你的血也闻起来怪怪的
And your blood smells funny, too.
别担心 孩子
Don't you worry, son.
睡一觉就好了
Nothing a good night's kip won't sort.
抱歉啦
Sorry about that.
你昨晚喝什么了
What the hell did you drink last night?
好了
Right.
刚说到哪了
Where were we?
不出所料
To the surprise of no one,
那傻X虫人又飞着玩了
that moron Swatto went for another joy flight,
暴露了我们的位置
giving away our position.
更要命的是 桑地诺人
Even better, the Sandinistas
是带着俄罗斯的特种部队来的
brought Russian special forces with them.
但对超人类来说没什么
Though that didn't matter much to the Supes.
他们是自己人
Those are my men!
你 跟着我 冲
You, stay with me! Go!
干 干 干
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
火药 你特么能不能停下来
Gunpowder! Will you please fucking stop?
我的天
Oh, God.
他们杀了士兵男孩
They killed Soldier Boy.
- 啥 谁 - 俄罗斯人
- What? Who? - The Russians.
他们有某种枪或武器之类的东西
They had some kind of gun or-or weapon or something.
- 那不可能 - 不
- That's impossible. - No!
- 我们都看到了 我们都看到了
- We saw it. We saw it.
他们抬走了他的尸体
They took his body.
我失去了一百一十六名士兵
I lost 116 men.
而沃特被完全豁免了
And Vought got full immunity.
就是那天 我决定要他们血债血还
That was the day I decided to make them pay.
这故事可太美了
Well, ain't that a wonderful story.
告诉我 格蕾丝
Tell me, Grace,
俄罗斯人把超级枪
where did the Ivans take this...
带到哪里去了
Supe Gun?
铁幕政策之后 踪迹都消失了
The trail went cold behind the iron curtain.
真的
It's the truth.
我的能力仅限于此
My reach only goes so far.
你知道士兵男孩对我家人做了什么
You knew what Soldier Boy did to my family,
你不觉得我需要知道真相吗
but you didn't think I needed to know the truth?
没那么简单
It wasn't that simple.
马文 休伊 你们先出去
Marvin, Hugh, give us the room.
你在贝卡失踪之后找到我
You came to me after Becca disappeared
跟我保证拿到祖国人的人头
and promised me Homelander's head.
而一直以来
And all this time,
你都知道怎样能做到
you knew there was something that could do the job,
却闭口不谈
and you never said a fucking word.
不管这武器是什么
Whatever this weapon is,
不一定能对祖国人有效
it probably won't work on Homelander.
- 如果有效呢 - 那更糟
- And what if it does? - Even worse.
因为他不会是事情的结局
Because it wouldn't end with him.
你只会杀死一个又一个超人类
You'd go after another Supe, then another,
直到杀死所有超人类
then all of them.
如果你早点告诉我
If you'd have told me about this sooner,
祖国人大概已经死了
Homelander might already be dead.
瑞恩也就不用四处逃命
Ryan wouldn't be running from one safe house to the next,
担心他那神经老爸什么时候会从天而降
wondering when his nutter dad's gonna drop out of the sky.
而贝卡
And Becca...
贝卡或许还会活着
Becca might still be alive.
而因为这个
And for that...
我绝不会原谅你
...I'll never fucking forgive you.
这从来就跟瑞恩和贝卡无关
This was never about Ryan or Becca.
都不过是私心
It was always selfish.
一直都仅仅是为了你自己
Always and only for you.
因为你想要向这个世界发泄你心中的怒火
For the hate inside that you want to let loose on the world.
我本想着你变了 但我错了
I thought maybe you changed, but I was wrong.
你和你爸一样
You are your father.
一直都是
Always have been.
- 怎么了 - 我们走
- What happened? - We're off.
布彻 等等 你要去哪
Butcher, wait up. Where-where are you going?
- 城里 - 我什么时候会再见到你
- The city. - When will I see you again?
不会见到了 对你不安全
You won't. Ain't safe for you.
等等
Wait!
- 你在说什么 - 我得走了
- What are you talking about? - I got to go.
- 瑞恩 放手 - 不要
- Ryan, let go. - No.
你说过你会照顾好我
You said you'd always watch out for me.
- 你答应过我的 - 瑞恩 放手
- You promised! - Ryan, let go.
- 我不让你走 - 或许是我不想看到你
- I won't let you! - Well, maybe I don't want to look at you.
在你对我的贝卡做了那样的事后 你有想过吗
After what you done to my Becca. Did you ever think about that?
我恨你
I hate you.
如果叶甫根尼弄疼了你 我先道个歉
Sorry if Yevgenny got a little rough.
他对你日了他老婆还怀恨在心
He's still a bit bitter you ate his wife's anus.
你找我来干吗 妮娜
Why am I here, Nina?
你还记得米哈伊尔·彼得罗夫吗
Do you remember Mikhail Petrov?
你等着他回家 他从他那小面包车下车
You wait for him to come home. He step out of his minivan.
你袭击他 他把你手中匕首打掉
You attack. He knocks the blade from your hand,
然后你就用那台本田奥德赛的侧滑门
so you slam this Honda Odyssey minivan sliding doors
一遍又遍地夹他的脖子
on his neck over and over
直到他...
until he's...
人头落地
decapitated.
艺术一般 谁能说不是呢
Art. Who can define it?
然后你发现他年轻的新娘
Then you discovered his young bride
就坐在副驾驶
in the passenger seat,
而我的塞尔奇从不留活口
and my Sergei does not leave a witness behind.
雪莉在哪
Where is Cherie?
我不知道
I don't know.
她在巴约内有个藏身地
She had a place in Bayonne
我上次在那看到她的
last time I saw her.
为什么
Why?
因为没人偷她的海洛因
'Cause nobody stole heroin from her.
她却偷我的
She stole it from me.
我会让她死个痛快
I will give her a quick death, pazhalsta,
也不会亏待你的
and I will make this worth your while.
我不会再做这种事了
I don't do that shit anymore.
人是不会变的
Nobody changes, hmm?
你的安全词是什么来着
What was your safe word again?
用狗链和项圈的时候 是什么来着
When I used the dog collar and the strap-on? What was it?
文森特·卡塞尔
Vincent Cassel.
你就像条小疯狗
You are like rabid little doggy
谁牵着绳子就效忠谁
but loyal to whoever holds this chain.
在威廉·布彻之前效忠我
Before William Butcher, it was me.
我之前 效忠你爸爸
Before me, it was your daddy.
但你总是很听话 塞尔盖
But you always heel, Sergei.
不是塞尔盖
Not Sergei.
是塞尔奇
Serge.
那是很久之前的事了
And that was a long time ago.
我现在为中情局干活 妮娜
Who I am now is someone who works for the CIA, Nina.
如果你不想
So unless you want
让政府调查你
the full weight of the government up your ass...
就让我走
...I'm leaving.
我们都不在乎政府
We both have had bigger things than the government
的调查
up our asses.
想想我的建议
Just think about my offer.
走吧 快跑 小狗狗
Go on, scamper away, little doggy.
- 欢迎回来 哥们 - 欢迎
- welcome home, brother. - Hear! Hear!
感谢 祖国人
Oh, thanks, Homelander.
这对我意义重大
This literally means everything to me.
- 敬我们 - 敬我们
- To us. - To us.
好的
Ah! Here we are.
很好
Excellent. Okay,
我冒昧地先点好了菜
so, I took the liberty of ordering for all of us,
但我肯定你会喜欢的
but I'm pretty sure you're gonna love my selection. Okay?
谢谢 先生
Thank you, gentlemen.
好的
Yes, sir.
- 我能吃点面包什么的吗 - 别扫兴
- Could I just get some... some bread? - Come on, now.
你又归队了 伙计
You're back in the big leagues, buddy.
要给你最好的
Nothing but the best for you.
我好饿
I'm so hungry.
知道我最近在读谁的书吗
Know who I've been reading up on lately?
马丁·路德·金博士
Dr. Martin Luther King.
越来越能和他共鸣
Well, my relationship with King has deepened of late.
他被贬低
He was, uh, villainized.
被迫害 却依然直言不讳
Persecuted. Spoke truth to power.
就像我 很疯狂 但是
Just like me. It's crazy. But...
我们都到达过巅峰
we've both been to the mountaintop,
我们都见过应许之地
and we've seen the promised land.
我向人们展示了真实的我
I showed people the real me,
他们因此而喜欢我
and they loved me for it.
他们真的喜欢我
I mean, they fucking loved me.
要是我早点知道就好了
If only I'd known that sooner.
有很多我一直想做的事
There's always been so, so many things
我想做 现在终于可以做了
I want to do, and now I can do them all, finally.
而且没人能阻止我
And no one can stop me.
没有人
Nobody.
终于自由了
Free at last.
真好
Oh! Excellent.
深海
Deep,
- 这个是给你的 大家伙 - 我
- that's for you, big guy. - Me?
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
好极了
Wonderful.
主厨的招牌
Chef's specialty.
一道韩国菜
It is a South Korean delicacy.
我的天 这是蒂莫西
Holy shit, it's Timothy.
我的天
Oh, my God.
蒂莫西 他是我朋友
That's Timoth... He's my friend.
我不能吃它 我不会吃它的
I, uh, I can't eat him. I'm not gonna eat him. I can't...
- 你可以的 深海 - 不 我不能
- Oh, yes, you can, Deep. - No, I'm not gonna...
蒂莫西非常好吃
Timothy is fucking delicious.
他在求我放过他
He's-he's begging for his life.
他有孩子
He has kids.
卡桑德拉: 吃掉那只章鱼
嘿 深海
Hey, Deep?
什么
What?
吃了蒂莫西
Eat fucking Timothy.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他在祈求 他在求我
He's praying. He's praying.
他不好吃吗
Wasn't that delicious?
该死
Come on.
你真该看看他今天的样子
You should have seen him today.
布彻先生
Monsieur Charcutier?
你怎么能给那样的人工作
How do you work for a man like that?
你也为他工作
You work for him, too.
我在这都是因为你
I'm only here because you are.
我们走吧
But let's just leave.
去马赛
We can go to Marseille.
那该多好 是吧
Wouldn't that be nice, huh?
好的
All right, let's have it.
你这一天都去哪了
Where the fuck you been all day?
我被小妮娜扣住了
I was, uh, detained by Little Nina.
谁
Who's that?
小妮娜
Little Nina?
那个俄国荡妇找你干什么
And what does that Russian slag want with you?
说来话长
It's a long story.
等下
Hang about.
这是个宝库啊 弗兰基
This is a fucking gold mine, Frenchie.
安排你 我和小妮娜见个面
Set up a meeting with you, me and Little Nina.
不不不 这是个非常不好的主意
No, no, no. This is a very, is a very bad idea.
这主意真他妈棒极了
No, Frenchie, it's a very fucking good idea.
走 拿上电话
Go on. Get on the phone,
现在就去给她打电话
give her a call right now.
是的 先生
Oui, monsieur.
我们见她做什么呢
And what are we doing this for?
因为 小伙子 我们要去俄国了
'Cause, my son, we're going to Russia.
- 嘿 在忙吗 - 嘿
- Hey. Do you have a sec? - Hey. Hey.
嗯 进来
Yeah, yeah. Come in.
谢谢
Thanks. Um...
我找制片人说了
So I went to talk to the producers,
我家里有些急事
to tell them that I had a family emergency
我得退出
and I have to bow out.
好的 很好
Good. That's-that's really good.
但是 我到那里的时候
But, uh, you know, when I got there, I...
我告诉他们我渴望加入这个团队
I told them I was thrilled to join the team.
不 阿莱克斯 这是个错误
No. Alex, Alex, that's-that's a mistake.
在戒毒所时
I was in rehab,
为了拿到止痛药 我什么事都做得出来
would've killed my mother for some oxy.
经理放弃了我 沃特 所有人
Manager bailed on me, Vought, everyone.
但是你没有离开
But you didn't leave.
所以你认为我现在会离开你吗
So do you really think I'm gonna bail on you now?
我很混蛋
I'm an asshole,
但是还没混到那种程度
but I'm not that much of an asshole.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
得有人支持你
Someone's got to have your back.
来吧
Come on, then.
说出来
Let's hear it.
我是个该死的怪物 居然那样对待那孩子
I'm a fucking monster for what I done to the kid.
不是的
No.
我懂的 也许大家都不理解
The others don't get it, but I-I do.
对决开始了
The gloves are off.
如果我学到了什么
If there's anything that I've learned...
搞毛
What the fuck?
好的
Well,
你们历经千辛万苦
this has been quite a long road for all of you.
向我们展示了英雄们所能做的极致
You've shown us the best of what heroes can be.
两名七人队的新成员
The first of the two selections,
第一位是
and the newest member of The Seven is...
超音速
Supersonic.
欢迎
Welcome.
谢谢您
Thank you, sir.
万众瞩目
Well... this is it.
七人队的最后一名新成员
The final new member of The Seven is...
七海之王 深海
...Lord of the Seven Seas, the Deep.
上台来
Get up here, you.
好的
All right.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
- 见到你很开心 - 我也是
- Good to see you. - You, too.
- 恭喜 - 恭喜
- Congratulations, bro. - You, too.
好的 很遗憾 二位必须离开舞台
All right, well, unfortunately, it won't be either of you two.
我相信你们可以理解 这个经历也是
I'm sure you understand, you just can't put a price
- 非常宝贵的 - 请挂上斗篷离开吧
- on experience. - Please hang up your capes and go.
现在 深海 我要说
Now, Deep, I got to say, I am, uh,
坦白的说 我很感动也备受启发
well, frankly, I'm moved and inspired
对于星光选择了你 并且原谅了你
that Starlight here has chosen to forgive you.
我接受你的道歉 深海
I accept your apology, Deep.
你应该有第二次机会
You deserve a second chance.
谢谢你 星光 看来我们都成长了
Thank you, Starlight. Looks like we've all grown.
说明一下 让你回来
Just to be clear, it wasn't my idea
并不是我的主意
to bring you back, buster.
和我没关系 是星光坚持的
Not at all. Starlight here insisted on it.
但是 你得保持距离了 伙计
But you keep your distance, pal,
因为 嗯
because, uh, well...
她现在是我的女朋友了
...she's my girl now.
抱歉 我不能再保守这个秘密了
Sorry, I-I can't keep it a secret anymore.
是时候让大家都知道了
It's time we let the world know.
星光和我相爱了
Starlight and I are in love.
超话 组国之光
#HomeLight.
- 卡 非常好 - 什么
- Cut! Incredible. - Huh?
- 太棒了 - 我的天 - 这剧本绝了
- That fucking plays, man. - Oh, my God! - That plays like hell.
- 完美 - 观众一定会喜欢的
- That was perfect. Yeah, yeah. - People are gonna love it.
真的不敢相信
Incredible! Yes!
非常完美
Okay, that was perfect, uh,
但是 星光 别表现得那么震惊
but, Starlight, I need you to be not so shocked.
好的 我们再来一次
All right, well, uh, let's go again.
星光
Starlight?
可以吗
We good?
准备好了么
We ready?
嗯 我们再来一次
Yeah. Let's, uh, let's go again.
- 好的 再来一次 - 再拍一次
- Okay. Going again. - Yeah, one more. Great.
从你那句台词 祖国人
Uh, take it from your line, Homelander.
好的
You got it.
All right.
- 好姑娘 - 开始
- That a girl. - And... action.
我不能再保守这个秘密了
I just can't keep it a secret anymore.
是时候向大家宣布了
Come on, it's time we let the world know.
各位
Um, everybody,
我和星光相爱了
Starlight and I are in love.
超话 祖国之光
#HomeLight.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现